woojr.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy Statement | Woo! Jr. Kids Activities

**Woo! Jr. Kids Activities Network** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate a firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website and our partner websites at AnimalJr.com and FantasyJr.com.

If you wish to learn more about online privacy and advertising standards, please visit the IAB (Interactive Advertising Bureau) [website](http://www.iab.net/privacymatters).

**Personally Identifiable Information**

We only collect personally identifiable information when you **specifically** provide it to us, as in the case of signing up for our email newsletter or leaving a comment on one of our pages. This site contains a blog and may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Every single website you visit on the internet collects this same information.

Email addresses collected in comment forms on our sites are collected only for verification / anti-spam purposes. Comments do not register you for any mailings, newsletters, or other mass communications from the Woo! Jr. Kids Activities Network.

Email addresses collected via our newsletter signup form are **never** sold or rented to third parties. We use AWeber for our mailing system and comply with the highest ethical email marketing standards and go above and beyond CAN-SPAM guidelines. In order to be added to our newsletter mailing list, you must explicitly opt-in, actively giving us permission to send you emails. This permission may be withdrawn at any time by clicking the _Unsubscribe_ link included in every communication we send you.

**Links to Other Websites**

This site contains links to other sites. Woo! Jr. Kids Activities Network is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Age Restrictions  
**  
You must be 13 years of age or older to leave a comment on any of the Woo! Jr. websites. We prohibit registration by children under the age of 13 for all interactive portions of the Sites including chats and message boards. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, feel free to [contact us](https://www.woojr.com/contact).

**Disclosures**

Read our disclosure policy [here ](https://www.woojr.com/disclosures/)– in a nutshell, we **always** disclose any potential conflicts of interest and will **never** knowingly mislead our site visitors.

**Advertising Partners**

About Google AdSense and the DoubleClick DART cookie:

  * Google as a third party vendor uses cookies to serve ads on this site
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to this site’s visitors based on their visits to this site and other sites elsewhere on the Internet
  * You can opt out of the use of the DART cookie if you wish by visiting [Google’s ad and content network privacy policy page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)
